GitHub <noreply@github.com>

Hi @!

Help us secure your GitHub account by verifying your email address ). This will let you receive notifications and password resets from GitHub.

Verify email address
Button not working? Paste the following link into your browser:
https://github.com/users/emails/16479551/confirm_verification/b58fcb1feee9f580eef95f1c41de8

You’re receiving this email because you recently created a new GitHub account or added a new email address. If this wasn’t you, please ignore this email.

Sent with <3 by GitHub.
GitHub, Inc. 88 Colin P Kelly Jr Street
San Francisco, CA 94107